BILOXI CALLIGRAPHY is heavier version with calligraphic strokes of a handwritten font of mine called "Biloxi Script".

This is a demo version. Free for personal use only. For commercial use please visit rolandhuse.com or contact@rolandhuse.com

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/rolandhusedesign

